Guide to the Time Inc. Index Cards 1933-1993, undated MS 3009-RG 4
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Index Cards
1933-1993, undated
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 4
260 Linear feet in 258 record cartons which include 173 reels of microfilm
Time Inc. Index Cards span from approximately 1933 to 1993 and contain groups of index cards used by Time Inc. staff for writing, searching, and cross referencing subject terms related to Time Inc.'s major magazines, and as directories for published books and interviews.
Provenance
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Archival Materials Note
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers. Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use.
Arrangement Note
Organized into 11 series:
Series I: Discover
Series II:Life
Series III: Life International
Series IV: People
Series V: Sports Illustrated
Series VI: Subject Files
Series VII: Time
Series VIII:Time Advertising Promotion
Series IX: Time Canada
Series X: Time Inc. History Project
Series XI: Time International
Series XII: Time-Life International Advertising Promotion
Series XIII: Unfiled
Scope and Contents Note
The Time Inc. Index Cards span from approximately 1933 to 1993 and contain groups of index cards used by Time Inc. staff for writing, searching, and cross referencing materials related to Time Inc.'s major magazines, and as directories for published books and interviews. The major publications such as Time, Life, Discover, People, and Sports Illustrated each have a subject index. The majority of index cards provide a subject term, a brief description of a topic, and a date when the topic was covered within the associated magazine. There is also a section of general subjects that is not linked to a specific publication.
Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Card indexes; Time, inc. -- Archives
- Series I: Discover, 1980-1987; 162197; 2 Linear feet (2 boxes) (Offsite-box 176-177)
  Arrangement Note
  All materials in this series are arranged in original alphabetical order.
  Scope and Contents Note
  Discover contains index cards that serve as a subject index for Discover magazine.The index cards provide a subject term, a brief description of a topic, and the date the topic was covered in the magazine. The topics covered include people, places, events, organizations, and objects. Only subjects starting with the letters C through Z are covered in this series.
- Series II: Life, 1936-1987; 162281; 19 Linear feet (17 boxes, 168 reels of microfilm)
  Life contains index cards and microfilm images of index cards that act as a subject cross-reference to the American version of Life magazine. Each index card contains a subject term, a brief overview of a topic, and a date in which the topic was covered. Topics covered on the index cards include people, places, events, organizations, and objects. Dates on microfilm refer to the original contents and not the date of microfilm creation.
  The materials in this series are kept in their original order of chronological groups. The original alphabetical arrangement within each group is also maintained.
  - 1936-1943
    - C-Z (microfilm) (Offsite-box 3329)
  - 1944-1951
    - A-Sk (microfilm) (Offsite-box 3329)
    - Sk-ZY (microfilm) (Offsite-box 3330)
  - 1952-1961
    - Cards, 162282 (Offsite-box 186)
    - A-Ny (microfilm) (Offsite-box 3330)
    - Ny-Z (microfilm) (Offsite-box 3331)
  - 1962-1972, 162283
    - AAA Jewelers Messenger Service -- Automobiles, 162284 (Offsite-box 186)
    - Automobiles -- Brabham-Repco, 162285 (Offsite-box 187)
    - Brabourne, Amanda -- Clubs, 162286 (Offsite-box 188)
    - Clubs -- Driving Ranges, 162287 (Offsite-box 189)
    - Driving the Pizza Parties From the Temple -- Funerals, 162288 (Offsite-box 190)
    - Funerals -- Ho Chi Minh, 162289 (Offsite-box 191)
    - Ho Chi Minh -- Kennedy Memorial Library, 162290 (Offsite-box 192)
    - Kennedy Memorial Library -- Lyon, Fred, 162291 (Offsite-box 193)
    - Lyon, Fred -- Movies, 162292 (Offsite-box 194)
    - Movies -- Paintings, 162293 (Offsite-box 195)
    - Paintings -- Rembar, Charles, 162294 (Offsite-box 196)
    - Rembrandt Van Vijn -- Shoes, 162295 (Offsite-box 197)
    - Shoes -- Tents, 162296 (Offsite-box 198)
    - Tents -- Wayman, Stan, 162297 (Offsite-box 199)
    - Wayman, Stan -- Zygielbaum, Joseph, 162867 (Offsite-box 200)
    - A-Ga (microfilm) (Offsite-box 3331)
    - Ga-Z (microfilm) (Offsite-box 3332)
  - 1978-1987, 162622
    - A&M -- Burghley House, 162817 (Offsite-box 200)
    - Burk, Dwight -- O'Neill, Terry, 162818 (Offsite-box 203)
    - O'Neill, Terry -- Zwillinger, Rhonda, 162819 (Offsite-box 204)
- Series III: Life International, approximately 1946-1965; 162326; 2.1 Linear feet (2 boxes, 5 reels of microfilm)
  Life International contains index cards that act as a subject cross-reference for the version of Life magazine that was produced for audiences outside of the United States. Index cards within this series contain a subject term, a brief overview of a topic, and a date in which the topic was covered within its respective magazine. While the majority of subseries contain subjects with letters ranging from A through Z, some subseries may be missing alphabetical subject areas. Life en Espanol includes microfilm of index cards. The microfilm does not have dates so it isn't clear if it is a duplication of the physical cards or unique material.
  The materials in this series are divided into 13 subseries: Life ABC/Car (1959,1964), Life Caribbean (1964), Life Continent (1964), Life DF Mexico (1964), Life English (1959-1965), Life en Espanol (1953-1959), Life Europe (1961-1962), Life Ex-Europe (1964), Life International (1946-1958), Life Mexico (1959, 1964), Life Spanish (1964), and Life Sterling (1964).
  Since Life International is compromised of an amalgamation of multiple magazines across a broad geography, the materials are divided into subseries that reflect the multiple international publications that Life published and the specific geographical areas those publications were released in. All the materials are kept in their original order and are in alphabetical order.
  - Subseries I: Life ABC/Car., 1959, 1964; 162332 (Offsite-box 201)
  - Subseries II: Life Caribbean, 1964; 162335 (Offsite-box 201)
  - Subseries III: Life Continent, 1964; 162330 (Offsite-box 202)
  - Subseries IV: Life DF Mexico, 1964; 162336 (Offsite-box 201)
  - Subseries V: Life English, 1959-1965; 162327 (Offsite-box 201-202)
  - Subseries VI: Life en Espanol, 1953-1959
    - Cards, 1953-1959; 162331 (Offsite-box 201)
    - Microfilm, undated (Offsite-box 3332)
  - Subseries VII: Life Europe, 1963-1964; 162341 (Offsite-box 202)
  - Subseries VIII: Life European, 1961-1962; 162342 (Offsite-box 202)
  - Subseries IX: Life Ex-Europe, 1964; 162343 (Offsite-box 202)
  - Subseries X: Life International, 1946-1958; 162345 (Offsite-box 202)
  - Subseries XI: Life Mexico, 1959, 1964; 162338 (Offsite-box 201)
  - Subseries XII: Life Spanish, 1964; 162337 (Offsite-box 201)
  - Subseries XIII: Life Sterling, 1964; 162344 (Offsite-box 202)
- Series IV: People, 1974-1987; 162623; 18 Linear feet (18 boxes)
  The index cards in this series are kept in their original order of two chronological groups: 1974-1982 and 1983-1987. The original alphabetical arrangement within each group is also maintained.
  People contains index cards with subject terms related to topics covered in People magazine. Each index card contains a subject term, a brief description of a topic, and a date in which the topic was covered in the magazine. The topics covered include people, places, events, organizations, and objects.
  - 1974-1982, 162624
    - Aaker, Lee -- Bible, 162625 (Offsite-box 205)
    - Bible -- Charities, 162626 (Offsite-box 206)
    - Charities -- Dolls, 162627 (Offsite-box 207)
    - Dolls -- Goddard, John, 162628 (Offsite-box 208)
    - Goddard, John Mrs. (Susan), P. -- Jones, James, 162629 (Offsite-box 209)
    - Jones, James -- McNally, Joe, 162630 (Offsite-box 210)
    - McNally, Joe -- Oak School (Ill.), 162631 (Offsite-box 211)
    - Oaksey, John -- Records, 162632 (Offsite-box 212)
    - Records -- Songwriters' Hall of Fame, 162707 (Offsite-box 213)
    - Song-writing Soprao with Fragile Vocal Cords Casts Here Sexy Spell on Rock, A -- Wadsworth, Nelson, 162708 (Offsite-box 214)
    - Wadsworth, Nelson -- ZZ Top (Group), 162709 (Offsite-box 215)
  - 1983-1987, 162710
    - Aafjes, Trudy -- Ariona Daily Star (Newspaper), 162711 (Offsite-box 215)
    - Arizona State -- Civil Rights, 162713 (Offsite-box 216)
    - Civil Rights -- G.I.F.T. Procedure (Gamete Intrafallopian Tube Transfer), 162714 (Offsite-box 217)
    - Gifts -- Lopez, Andrea, 162715 (Offsite-box 218)
    - Lopez, Antonio -- Pet Aerobics, 162716 (Offsite-box 219)
    - Pet Bereavement -- South Bronx Was Getting A Bad Rap Until A Club Called Disco Fever Came Along, The, 162717 (Offsite-box 220)
    - South Carolna -- Zendejas Boys Find Life Is A Relative Kick, The, 162718 (Offsite-box 221)
    - Zendejas, Genaro -- ZZ Top (Group), 162719 (Offsite-box 222)
- Series V: Sports Illustrated, 1954-1983; 162720; 34 Linear feet (34 boxes)
  Sports Illustrated contains index cards that act as a cross-reference for subjects covered in Sports Illustrated magazine. Each index card cotains a subject term, a brief description of a topic, and a date in which the topic was covered in the magazine. The topics covered include people, places, events, organizations, and objects.
  The index cards in this series are kept in their original order of three chronological groups: 1954-1967, 1968-1982, and 1983. The original alphabetical arrangement within each group is also maintained.
  - 1954-1967, 162721
    - Basketball-Professional -- Bridge, 162722 (Offsite-box 222)
    - Bridge -- Collier, Blanton, 162723 (Offsite-box 223)
    - Collier, Blanton -- Du Quoin, Ill., 162724 (Offsite-box 224)
    - Du Quoin, Ill. -- Galbreath, John W., 162725 (Offsite-box 225)
    - Galbreath, John -- He Flies On One Wing, 162732 (Offsite-box 226)
    - Heft, Herb -- Jansco, Mrs. Paulie, 162733 (Offsite-box 227)
    - Jansco, Paulie (Joey) -- Long Beach-to-San Francisco Ocean Powerboat Race, 162734 (Offsite-box 228)
    - Longboat -- Moscosco, Teodora, 162735 (Offsite-box 229)
    - Moscow, Idaho -- Parsons, Garrett S., 162736 (Offsite-box 230)
    - Parsons, George A. -- Romig, Joe, 162737 (Offsite-box 231)
    - Romig, Joe -- Skobikova, Lydia, 162738 (Offsite-box 232)
    - Skocylas, Adam -- Tennis, 162739 (Offsite-box 233)
    - Tennis -- Weight Lifting-Scoreboard, 162807 (Offsite-box 234)
    - Weight Lifting-Scoreboard -- Zyl, Annette Van, 162808 (Offsite-box 235)
  - 1968-1982, 162809
    - A'A (Lava) -- Archibald, Nate, 162810 (Offsite-box 235)
    - Archibald, Nate -- Bignotti, George, 162811 (Offsite-box 236)
    - Bignotti, George -- Castro, Fidel, 162812 (Offsite-box 237)
    - Castro, Fidel -- DeLillo, Don, 162813 (Offsite-box 238)
    - Delle, Bob -- Florida, 162814 (Offsite-box 239)
    - Florida -- Guerrero, Pedro, 162815 (Offsite-box 240)
    - Guerrero, Pedro -- Instruction-baseball, 162816 (Offsite-box 241)
    - Instructions-baseball -- Larouche, Pierre, 167980 (Offsite-box 243)
    - Larouche, Pierre -- Meisler, Andy, 167981 (Offsite-box 244)
    - Meisler, Andy -- Nicklaus, Jackie, 167982 (Offsite-box 245)
    - Nicklaus, Jackie -- Powers ,Richie, 167983 (Offsite-box 246)
    - Powers, Richie -- Scharfman, Herb, 167984 (Offsite-box 247)
    - Scharfman, Herb -- Staubach, Roger, 167985 (Offsite-box 248)
    - Staubach, Roger -- Uecker, Bob, 167986 (Offsite-box 249)
    - Uecker, Bob -- Yaocho!, 167987 (Offsite-box 250)
    - Yapple, John -- 1,000 to 1 Shot, 167988 (Offsite-box 251)
  - 1983-1987, 162864
    - AAA Championship (Britain) -- College Football, 168003 (Offsite-box 251)
    - College Football -- Hockey, 168004 (Offsite-box 252)
    - Hockey -- Naso, Bob, 168005 (Offsite-box 253)
    - Nassau Point, N.Y. -- SQW, 168006 (Offsite-box 254)
    - SQW -- Zwink, Joel, 168007 (Offsite-box 255)
- Series VI: Subject Files, approximately 1940-1990; 135564; 41 Linear feet (41 boxes)
  The Subject files contain index cards which act as a cross-reference for subject terms. Cards contain the term that a user would search by and then directs the user to the appropriate term under which materials related to that topic are filed. Some cards also include related topics. Topics that are covered include people, places, events, organizations, and objects. One photo was discovered with the materials and is filed alongside the index cards in Box 34.
  The materials in this series are arranged in their original alphabetical order by subject.
  - A1 -- Alaska Highway, 135565 (Offsite-box 1)
  - Alaska Highway Pipeline Project -- Anderson's Raiders, 135566 (Offsite-box 2)
  - Andes -- Association of Theaters of the Paris Opera, 135567 (Offsite-box 3)
  - Assoc. of Theater Benefit Agents -- Bidding Signals, 135568 (Offsite-box 4)
  - Biddle Foundation, Margaret T. -- Building Inspectors Union, Allied, 135569 (Offsite-box 5)
  - Building Investment Trust -- Cayman, 135570 (Offsite-box 6)
  - Cayman Islands -- Cirques, 135571 (Offsite-box 7)
  - Cirrhosis of the Liver -- Committee For Freedom For University Clergy, 135572 (Offsite-box 8)
  - Committee for Freedom in the Church -- Consumer Contracts, 135573 (Offsite-box 9)
  - Consumer Co-op Bank -- D.R.V, 135574 (Offsite-box 10)
  - D.R.V. (Daily Reference Value) -- Dolby Stereo, 135575 (Offsite-box 11)
  - Dole-Grassley Bill -- Emergency Support Vessel, 135576 (Offsite-box 12)
  - Emergency Surgery -- Farm Credit System, 135577 (Offsite-box 13)
  - Farm Credit System Capital Corporation -- Fort Mott, 135580 (Offsite-box 14)
  - Fort Myers Tangelo -- Get Ahead Foundation, 135581 (Offsite-box 15)
  - Get America Back to Work Conference -- Harvard Negotiation Project, 135582 (Offsite-box 16)
  - Harvard-Newton Summer Program -- ICP (International Photographic Council), 135583 (Offsite-box 17)
  - I.C.R.C. (International Committee of the Red Cross) -- Interest Income, 135585 (Offsite-box 18)
  - Interest of Judgement -- J93-3, 135586 (Offsite-box 19)
  - J93-5 -- L.V.T.P.X.-2, 135587 (Offsite-box 20)
  - LVTUX -- Lord's Taverners, 135588 (Offsite-box 21)
  - Lordship of Manors -- Measure-Ins, 135589 (Offsite-box 22)
  - Measure of Economic Warfare -- Mohammedanism, 135590 (Offsite-box 23)
  - Mohammed's Youth -- National Cancer Authority, 135591 (Offsite-box 24)
  - National Cancer Center -- National Urban News, 135592 (Offsite-box 25)
  - National Urban Policy Conference -- Newswomen's Club of New York, 135593 (Offsite-box 26)
  - Newsworthy Children of Newsworthy Parents -- Operating Companies, 135594 (Offsite-box 27)
  - Operating Costs -- Paris Wall, 135595 (Offsite-box 28)
  - Paris Welsh Society -- PLOW (Political and Legislative Organizaion on Watch), 135596 (Offsite-box 29)
  - Plow Back Requirement -- Project Return (Connecticut), 135597 (Offsite-box 30)
  - Project Return (New York) -- Records (Documents), 135598 (Offsite-box 31)
  - Records (Phonograph) -- Ruckus Works, 135599 (Offsite-box 32)
  - Rudder Club -- Security Identification Procedures, 135600 (Offsite-box 33)
  - Security Imprinting and Processing Task Force -- Society of American Wood Engravers (S.A.W.E), 135601 (Offsite-box 34)
  - Society of American Woodworkers -- Stern College of Women, 135602 (Offsite-box 35)
  - Stern Community Law Firm -- Tatmadaw, 135603 (Offsite-box 36)
  - Tatoo Club of America -- Trainfare, 135604 (Offsite-box 37)
  - Trainfire -- United Parents Association, 135605 (Offsite-box 38)
  - United Parents Association of New York City -- War Centers, 135606 (Offsite-box 39)
  - War Chest Tours -- World Energy Conference, 135607 (Offsite-box 40)
  - World Energy Exposition -- Zytel, 136452 (Offsite-box 41)
- Series VII: Time, 1936-1987; 146736; 134 Linear feet (134 boxes)
  Time contains index cards that serve as a directory for subject terms for Time magazine. Each index card contains a subject term, a brief description of a topic related to that term, and the date when the topic was covered in the magazine. The topics covered include people, places, events, organizations, and objects.
  The cards are kept in original order of six chronological groups: 1936-1943, 1943-1950, 1951-1962, 1963-1967, 1968-1982, and World War II. The materials in the World War II group cover the period of 1939-1942. While the majority of groups contain cards beginning with letters A through Z, not all groups contain subject areas for every letter of the alphabet. All groups maintain their original order and are organized in alphabetical order by subject.
  - World War II, 1939-1942; 159296 (Offsite-box 92-93)
  - 1936-1943, 136453
    - A-17A -- Cleveland Trust Co., 136454 (Offsite-box 42)
    - Cleveland Union Terminal -- Greystone Press, 136455 (Offsite-box 43)
    - Gribble, Alphonse J. -- Mason Jar(s), 136456 (Offsite-box 44)
    - Masons -- Roosevelt, Quentin, 136457 (Offsite-box 45)
    - Roosevelt, Rebecca B.H. -- Vliet, Mrs. Frank, 136458 (Offsite-box 46)
    - Vobreiaux, La. -- Wilmot Woods, 146730 (Offsite-box 47)
  - 1943-1950, 146731
    - A-20 -- Art-Painting, 146732 (Offsite-box 47)
    - Art-Painting -- Bishop, John Peale, 146733 (Offsite-box 48)
    - Bishop, Julie -- Canada-Foreign Relations-Latin America, 146734 (Offsite-box 49)
    - Canada-Foriegn Relations-Latin America -- Comden, Betty, 146735 (Offsite-box 50)
    - Comden, Betty -- Diesel Locomotives, 146737 (Offsite-box 51)
    - Diesel Oil -- Farrell, James T., 146738 (Offsite-box 52)
    - Farrell, James T. -- Goerg, Edouard, 146739 (Offsite-box 53)
    - Goerg, Edouard -- Housing, 146740 (Offsite-box 54)
    - Housing -- Korea-Army, 146741 (Offsite-box 55)
    - Korea-Army -- McKenley, Herb, 149590 (Offsite-box 56)
    - McKenley, Herb -- Mitchell, Sidney C., 149592 (Offsite-box 57)
    - Mitchell, Stephen -- New Orleans, LA., 149595 (Offsite-box 58)
    - New Orleans, LA -- Picado, Teodoro, 149597 (Offsite-box 59)
    - Picado, Teodoro -- Religion, 149598 (Offsite-box 60)
    - Religion -- Seymour, Charles, 149599 (Offsite-box 61)
    - Seymour, Charles -- Tallinn, 149600 (Offsite-box 62)
    - Tallon, Ninon -- United Nations, 155692 (Offsite-box 63)
    - United Nations -- Van Nuys, Frederick, 155694 (Offsite-box 64)
    - Van Nuys, Frederick -- World War II-Prisoners and prisons-Russia, 155788 (Offsite-box 65)
    - World War II-Prisons and Prisoners-Russia -- ZZYZZ, Inc., 155789 (Offsite-box 66)
  - 1951-1962, 155791
    - A-3 Lifeboat -- Alzate Avendano, Gilberto, 155795 (Offsite-box 66)
    - Am, Mme. Nguyen Van -- Automobiles, 155797 (Offsite-box 67)
    - Automobiles -- Blackwood, Algernon, 155798 (Offsite-box 68)
    - Blackwood, Algernon -- Bronte, Charlotte, 155799 (Offsite-box 69)
    - Bronte, Charlotte -- Carybe, 155800 (Offsite-box 70)
    - Carzaou, Jean -- Clothings-Russia, 159271 (Offsite-box 71)
    - Clothings-Russia -- Crusader (Airplane), 159272 (Offsite-box 72)
    - Crusader F-8u -- Doucet, Mrs. Lawrence, 159273 (Offsite-box 73)
    - Doucett, George -- Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain, 159274 (Offsite-box 74)
    - Elizabeth II, Queen of Great Britain -- France-Armed Service-Conscription, 159275 (Offsite-box 75)
    - France-Army -- Goodrich, B.F., Co., 159276 (Offsite-box 76)
    - Goodrich, B.F. -- Hedrick, Zelma, 159277 (Offsite-box 77)
    - Hedtoft, Hans -- Ingersoll, Robert S., 159278 (Offsite-box 78)
    - Ingersoll, Robert S. -- Kennedy, John F.-Administration, 159279 (Offsite-box 79)
    - Kennedy, John F.-Administration -- Leaflets, 159280 (Offsite-box 80)
    - Leaflets -- McPheron, Wes, 159285 (Offsite-box 81)
    - McPherrin, John W. -- Miller, A.L., 159286 (Offsite-box 82)
    - Miller, Alfred J. -- Myers Rum, 159287 (Offsite-box 83)
    - My Father Told Me -- Nursery Schools, 159289 (Offsite-box 84)
    - Nurses and Nursing -- Pedregal, 159290 (Offsite-box 85)
    - Pedret, Master of -- Protestants, 159291 (Offsite-box 86)
    - Protestants -- Ritter, Thelma, 159292 (Offsite-box 87)
    - Ritter, Thelma -- Saturday Review, 159293 (Offsite-box 88)
    - Saturday Review -- Smoking, 159294 (Offsite-box 89)
    - Smoking -- Swangard, Erwin, 159295 (Offsite-box 90)
    - Swangard, Erwin -- Time, 159321 (Offsite-box 91)
    - Time -- United States-Commodity Credit Corp., 159322 (Offsite-box 94)
    - United States-Commodity Credit Corp. -- Verne, Jules, 159323 (Offsite-box 95)
    - Verne, Jules -- World War II-Atrocities, 159329 (Offsite-box 96)
    - World War II-Atrocities -- Zymosan, 159330 (Offsite-box 97)
  - 1963-1967, 159328
    - A & P -- Albany County, N.Y., 159331 (Offsite-box 97)
    - Albany Institute of History and Art -- Automobiles-Cadillac, 159332 (Offsite-box 98)
    - Automobiles-Cadillac -- Bolivia, 159333 (Offsite-box 99)
    - Bolivia -- Business and Industry, 159334 (Offsite-box 100)
    - Business and Industry -- Chicago, Ill., 159358 (Offsite-box 101)
    - Chicago, Ill. -- Connor of Allied, 159360 (Offsite-box 102)
    - Connors, Chuck -- Diefenbaker, John, 159361 (Offsite-box 103)
    - Diefenbaker, John -- Europe, 159362 (Offsite-box 104)
    - Europe -- Gallup Poll, 159363 (Offsite-box 105)
    - Gallup Poll -- Hamilton, Alvin, 159364 (Offsite-box 106)
    - Hamilton, Alvin -- In Bill Moore's Footsteps, 159365 (Offsite-box 107)
    - In Business -- Junction City Operation, 159366 (Offsite-box 108)
    - Junction City Operation -- Lawsuits, 159367 (Offsite-box 109)
    - Lawsuits -- Marca-Relli, Corrado, 159406 (Offsite-box 110)
    - Marceau, Marcel -- Monks, 159407 (Offsite-box 111)
    - Monks -- Negroes, 159408 (Offsite-box 112)
    - Negroes -- Organizations, 159409 (Offsite-box 113)
    - Organizations -- Politics, 159410 (Offsite-box 114)
    - Politics -- Red Sea, 159411 (Offsite-box 115)
    - Red Sea -- Salmonellosis, 159412 (Offsite-box 116)
    - Salmonellosis -- Smith, Ian, 159413 (Offsite-box 117)
    - Smith, Ian, P -- Taft, Robert A. Jr., 160869 (Offsite-box 118)
    - Taft, Robert Jr. -- Tower, John, 160870 (Offsite-box 119)
    - Tower, John -- Viet Nam-Relations-United States, 160871 (Offsite-box 120)
    - Viet Nam-Relations-United States -- World War II, 160872 (Offsite-box 121)
    - World War II -- Zycie Warszawy (Newspaper), 160873 (Offsite-box 122)
  - 1968-1982, 160882
    - A (Antibody) -- ABC, 160883 (Offsite-box 124)
    - ABC -- Assad, Hafez, 160884 (Offsite-box 125)
    - Assad, Hafez -- Batten, Barton, 160885 (Offsite-box 126)
    - Batten, Dwayne -- Books, 160887 (Offsite-box 127)
    - Books -- British Trident (ship), 160888 (Offsite-box 128)
    - British Union of Fascists -- Cancer, 160889 (Offsite-box 129)
    - Cancer -- Charlemagne, 160890 (Offsite-box 130)
    - Charlemagne -- Cohen, Maimon, (Dr.), 160891 (Offsite-box 131)
    - Cohen, Maimon M. (Dr.) -- Corporation, 160892 (Offsite-box 132)
    - Corporations -- Demise of the Moderate, 160893 (Offsite-box 133)
    - Demise of the Quickie Divorce -- Duncan, Isadora, 160894 (Offsite-box 134)
    - Duncan, Isadora -- Erika, 160895 (Offsite-box 135)
    - Eriksen, Ted -- Florida, 160896 (Offsite-box 136)
    - Florida -- Gardener, John C., 160898 (Offsite-box 137)
    - Gardner, John W. -- Greece, 160899 (Offsite-box 138)
    - Greece -- Heller, Walter, 160900 (Offsite-box 139)
    - Heller, Walter -- Hurst, Fannie, 160901 (Offsite-box 140)
    - Hurst, Hunter -- 'It's God's Will,', 160902 (Offsite-box 141)